# Ismail

## Engineer

**Q** 085772248579

ismailidn1@gmail.com

Kab. Bogor, Jawa Barat

#### SUMMARY

Majoring in Informatics Engineering. Easy to be inspired, to study effectively, and productively in order to advance professionally. Very excited about creating or building a system or program that will benefit others, particularly the process of making or developing it all together with the team in order to add new experience and knowledge

#### EXPERIENCE

Fullstack Engineer 07/2022 - Present

- · Technologies: NextJs, RedwoodJs, Tailwind CSS, AWS, Jest
- Develop and participate yellowgreens app and google reservation site for the company, creating a structure for integrating with AWS Platform

**Frontend Enginner** 02/2022 - 06/2022

SICEPAT EKSPRES INDONESIA

- Technologies: Laravel, JavaScript, JQuery ,CSS3, SCSS, HTML5,Git.
- Develop and participate in adding new features and maintaining existing features on Selene(DMS) web.
- Tools: Jira, Github, Github CI/CD, Slack, Discord.

Frontend Engineer Intern 08/2021 - 01/2022

Vidio

- Technologies: React.js, Typescript, TDD, Webpack, Jest, React Testing Library, ESLint, CSS3, SCSS, HTML5, JavaScript, Git, Storybook.
- · Develop and participate in adding new features and maintaining existing features on lite.vidio.com
- Tools: Pivotal Tracker, Github, Github CI/CD, Slack.

Frontend Engineer Intern 08/2020 - 10/2020

Loker Programmer

- Technologies: React.js, Tailwind Css, CSS3, HTML5, JavaScript (ES5 ES6), Git.
- Tools: Github

#### EDUCATION

Computer Science 2022

Pamulang University - Bachelor's degree

Successfuly build and deployed an seminar system to provide information on seminars/events at Pamulang University to lecturers and students, as for the attendance system, and printing of event tickets/certificates.

### CERTIFICATES

Sertifikasi Kompetensi Bidang Pengembangan Perangkat Lunak

11/2020 - 11/2023

Belajar Fundamental Front-End Web Development

05/2020 - 05/2023

Belajar Dasar Pemrograman Web

04/2020 - 04/2023

### SKILLS

SQL **HTML** Advanced Advanced CSS Intermediate Advanced Git Javascript Advanced **Typescript** Intermediate React.js Advanced Intermediate Jest Laravel Intermediate **React Testing Library** Advanced Bootstrap Intermediate Node Js Intermediate

React Native Intermediate Flutter Basic

### LANGUAGES

English Intermediate Bahasa Native